Content or something. Yeah nice man. How are you doing this morning? I'm doing good afternoon for you
Nice morning, still.
Awesome, awesome.
What do you call a phone?
I'm in Denver right now.
Okay, very cool.
beautiful city awesome yeah I've only been there like through the airport though
So I don't know I don't know too much about it, but uh, yeah, you're not miss not too much. No, fair enough.
Awesome, man.
Well, I'm glad we can hop on the call together today.
Um, my name is Austin, so I work with Misha closely on cube craft.
I'm one of the admins here.
So my goal at this call today is,
I'm just gonna try to figure out what your goals are
see if we can help you reach those goals and also give you the
have opportunity to figure out if we're a good match for your goals, right?
Worst case scenario, you have something in your back pocket. So I'm good.